Hatem Hamrouni

Full stack web developer & Designer

EXPERIENCE

Volunteer Coach

Monster gym - Kairouan

07/2017 - Present

Informed gym members about nutrition, lifestyle issues, and weight excercices.

Trainee - designer

Al-Nasr printing press, Kairouan

01/2020 - 02/2020

Freelance Designer

99designs.com

12/2015 - 09/2020

Design of Logos and packaging including:

- Creation of Manhattan eyeworks chelsea's logo.
- · Creation of Century & Co Real Estate's logo.
- Creation of logo for the website: https://www.eyeque.com/ and its mobile application which has been named as the best innovation in the Consumer Electronics Show, CES 2019.
- Etc..

EDUCATION

GoMyCode - Sousse

2021

Full stack Web Development certificate

Higher Institute Of Computer Science And Management - Kairouan

2013

Master degree in computer Networks And Distributed Applications

Higher Institute Of Computer Science And Management - Kairouan

2009

Licence in Online computer Services

Okba High School - Kairouan 2006 Baccalaureate of economy +216 96328718

rukfarfa@gmail.com Kairouan, Tunisia

SUMMARY

Creative Designer with more than 4 years of experience working in the Design field.

Achievements include winning than 35 contests in 99designs website. In addition, i'm a full stack web developer, Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease.

SKILLS

Graphic Design & illustration Advanced

Creativity Advanced

Programming Languages Intermediate

Computer proficiency Expert
Creativity Expert

LANGUAGES

Arabic Native

English Fluent

French Intermediate

CERTIFICATES

Training in ways of communication - SMART Formation school

IELTS - British council